# VIALLI KAVOO

DevOps Engineer

### INFO

#### **ADDRESS**

Nadine Gordimers Vej 10 st tv, København S, 2300, Denmark

#### PHONE

50163040

#### **EMAIL**

vialli\_kavoo@hotmail.com

#### DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

1991-01-02 India

#### NATIONALITY

Indian

## SKILLS

AWS

Openshift

Docker

Git

Jenkins Pipeline/Scripting

Databases

Maven, Gradle

Python

#### **PROFILE**

With an eye for detail, I love building scale-able, highly available infrastructure to support systems with the customer as the main focus. I have extensive experience in design and implementation of fully automated continuous integration, continuous delivery and deployment pipelines for projects in the financial domain. I have worked in multiple projects involving Cloud (AWS) usage and Platform as a Service (Openshift)

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

#### Senior Platform Engineer, Danske Bank

Copenhagen, Denmark

Aug 2017 - Present

Responsibilities include but not limited to

- CI/CD using Jenkins declarative pipelines and shared libraries,
  Azure DevOps and Octopus Deploy
- · Database migrations via flyway in the pipeline for version Control
- · Infrastructure on PaaS(Openshift) via yaml templates.
- · Config Management Via SourceControl
- Dockerise microservices, build and deploy them via pipelines to Openshift
- Metrics telemetry , visualisation, and alerting (Telegraf, Grafana, InfluxDB, OpsGenie)
- · Automatic provisioning of infrastructure via Terraform and Atlantis
- · Application performance monitoring and error tracking via Sentry
- · Code quality and security using SonarQube
- Open Source Security and License Compliance via BlackDuck
- · Secrets management via OpenSSL and AWS KMS
- · Log Management via ELK(Elastic, LogStash, Kibana) Stack
- Served as a friendly, hardworking, and punctual employee.
- Organized and prioritized work to complete assignments in a timely, efficient manner.

#### Senior Software Engineer, Larsen and Toubro Infotech Ltd

Multiple Locations

Nov 2012 — Aug 2017

ELK Stack, Splunk	
NGINX	
Metrics (Grafana, Telegraf, InfluxDB)	
Bash, Terminal	
Infrastructure as Code	

## LANGUAGES

English	
Hindi	
Marathi	
Danish	

## HOBBIES

Bouldering, Calisthenics, Cooking, Gaming

## LINKS

LinkedIn

Resume

**Github** 

My Wedding Project

Whilst working for Larsen and Toubro, i have consulted on multiple projects below:

Consultant to Nordea, Copenhagen, Denmark (March 2016 - Aug 2017):

I arrived in the bicycle capital of the world, Copenhagen, the Scandinavian gem and have been living here since March 2016. During my brief stint at Nordea Bank for a year, I worked in the Financial Planning Platform, and helped coordinate a largely manual process of releasing software into productions across 10 teams, whilst taking small chunks at a time and automating those. Amongst other tasks, i overlooked the infrastructure needed to keep the platform running. Planning Releases for the near future, coordinate with different teams, product owners and business people and advisors about the releases

Consultant to Standard Bank, Johannesburg, South Africa (June 2014 - Dec 2015):

I lived in the beautiful city of Johannesburg, South Africa for 18 months working with Standard Bank, the largest bank in South Africa, as an Infrastructure Engineer and a DevOps Practitioner. Working for a FX trading platform as a start to my DevOps journey was a steep learning curve. I helped the team build an automated deployment pipeline and move away from large bulky application servers to a more micro-service based approach. Helped the team embrace concepts of continuous integration, deployment and delivery. It is at this stage in my career, where i gained exposure to DevOps as an approach to advocate better communication and collaboration between development and operations. Among other things i helped the team to

- Transition from Maven to gradle as a build tool to automate the compilation, deployment and testing of Web and J2EE applications to the above platforms
- · Scripting in multiple languages like Jython, Bash, PowerShell
- Set Up Geneos Active Console for monitoring applications on the Production Stack
- Working with Architects, Project Managers, Vendors, Developers and Network Teams to implement Netscaler to run a High Availability environment in-case of a failover.
- Developed scripts to monitor applications to and perform automated failovers

## Junior Php Developer, Dongre Technoquip Mumbai, India Pvt Ltd

Jul 2012 — Oct 2012

As a newbie just out of college, this 3 month summer job gave me great exposure to how things actually work in the IT workplace!

- · Open source webmail (ie Roundcube mail)
- Automated the test taking process for new candidates by making an online quiz in PHP

## **EDUCATION**

#### Mumbai

#### Bachelor of Engineering, Mumbai University

Jun 2008 — Jun 2012

An 8 semester course, covering application of computing, mathematics and analytical ability to real life problems and making it easier by digitally implementing those.

#### REFERENCES

## Tanya Da Silva (Scrum Master/Project Manager)

Standard Bank, South Africa

bomberjill@gmail.com +27827772817

#### Peter Wennick (Direct Manager)

Danske Bank, Denmark

+4530368194

## Steen Kamby (Team Member)

Danske Bank

52398820

### Radu Oprica (Team Lead)

Danske Bank

53775702